

Jasmina Fabijan

jasminafabijan.com

Novi Sad, Serbia (UTC+1)

SUMMARY

HTML/CSS developer, web and UX designer with more than 8 years of experience designing and developing websites and web application. My HTML code is clean, well commented and W3C valid. As designer, I'm focused on clean, nice and useful things.

EXPERIENCE

HTML/CSS developer at CPV Lab Pro

Oct 2020 - Present

CPV Lab Pro is powerful tracking tool for marketing which helps users to test and optimize their campaigns.

- My major task was changing Bootstrap theme in this web application
- Occasional HTML updates on the promotional website

HTML/CSS developer, UI/UX designer at Ruoom Inc.

Jul 2019 - Present

The Ruoom Inc. created a simplified business management software with features like – client management, online booking, point-of-sale, staff management, scheduling. My job includes:

- Implementing components from the Bootstrap theme to HTML files
- Design and coding custom pages
- Providing solutions for the best user experiences
- Design and coding email templates

HTML/CSS developer at Ahead Technology

May 2019 - Sep 2020

Ahead Technology France's office aims to support the major local players in training, by providing them with adapted global solutions, allowing them to operate certification courses around popular standards in IS management. I had the following tasks:

- Convert XD to responsive HTML pages using Bootstrap 4
- Update design through CSS on existing platforms

HTML/CSS developer, UI/UX designer at GetMeAGuide

Feb 2018 - Apr 2019

Getmeaguide simplifies the process of finding a professional independent travel guides. All pages are based on the Bootstrap 4. My part in creating this service was:

- Converting PSD to HTML for two Landing pages
- Design and coding inner pages
- Design and coding emails
- Design implementations in Slim files

HTML developer at Golke.ca

Nov 2016 - May 2017

Golke is digital advertising agency responsible for managing clients social media budgets in financial services and e-commerce industries. My tasks was:

- Updating the content in HTML templates
- Design improvements of existing pages
- Creating different design for testing

HTML/CSS developer, UI/UX designer at Fusion Advisor

May 2014 - Present

Fusion Advisor is Financial Service. It gives one access to all financial accounts, with mission to help clients to manage their accounts more efficiently. In this Company I'm working on:

- UI/UX design of web application
- Creating responsive HTML pages using Bootstrap
- Design and development of Landing page
- Design and coding emails
- Design implementations in PHP files

HTML/CSS developer and web designer at Agavey

Oct 2012 - Feb 2014

Agavey was Home Maintenance Services Store, but the Company doesn't exist any more. This was my first job as web designer and developer and I have:

• designed and coded (with Bootstrap) whole website, from Homepage to the last step during the process of purchasing the service

jasminafabijan.com

- created website, including lot of forms, for Vendors
- created email templates with MailChimp

EDUCATION

Department of Finance, Banking and Insurance, Faculty of Economics, Novi Sad, Serbia.

CONTACT PORTFOLIO

jf@jasminafabijan.com